1 Sheriffs Ride, Brownsfield Farm, Netherstowe Lane, Lichfield WS13 8EQ

# Cade Meakin

cademeakin@gmail.com cademeakin.com

Mobile: 07432 174491

## **Profile**

I am an enterprising individual who works as a UI/UX Developer and Front-End Web Developer. Since completing my two year IT Diploma in 2017, I have continued to pursue and define my career in the IT and Creative Industry. I am currently a freelance web developer and employed as a part-time roofer whilst I study different computer languages and frameworks such as JavaScript, jQuery, Wordpress, PHP, MySQL, APIs, Python etc. using online courses. I am determined to continue my development as a UI/UX Designer and Front-End Web Developer.

## **Work Experience**

December 2020 -May 2021

#### **Switch Design Consultancy**

Junior Web Developer

- Creation and upkeep of client Wordpress sites using SCSS, PHP, HTML, JavaScript, Node, XD for designs etc.
- Agency work experience

August 2018 - October 2020

#### **Valpak Limited**

UI/UX Front End Web Developer

- Wire framing, Design and Development of company website, E-mail templates and other digital elements of the Company
- Updating and maintenance through Visual Studio servers and CMS (Sitefinity & Wordpress)

January 2018 - March

#### **Opus Digital Media**

Contract work - Multiple Projects

- Individually designing and creating the UI/UX of client web sites
- Updating and maintaining client websites

January 2018 - Current

#### **Freelance Web Design**

Sites can be found on Portfolio

• Designing, building and managing domain and hosting of sites

June 2017

#### Age UK Tamworth

30+ hours

- Managed and maintained the website of Age UK
- Uploaded documents and managed layout of the web page

June 2014

#### **Access Computers**

2 Weeks

- IT Trouble Shooting, Repairs and Maintenance
- Updated Databases

2014 - Current

#### Armaclad Ltd.

Industrial Roofing and Cladding

### **Skills**

HTML - CSS - SCSS - JavaScript - PHP - WordPress - Node - Gulp Advanced Custom Fields - Adobe XD/Photoshop - Visual Studio Code

## **Education**

2017 CCA HTML Level 1

**CCA** CSS Level 1

**CCA** JavaScript Level 1

#### 2015 - 2017 ICT Extended Diploma Level 3

South Staffordshire College, Tamworth

19 Units Including:

Client-Side Web Design - Created Web page

- Web Server Scripting Created multiple live server scripted functions
- Web Site Production Created complete and responsive web site
- Developing Computer Games Web application games
- Digital Graphics
- Animation
- Organisational Systems Security

Overall Grade: **DDD** 

#### 2010 - 2015 King Edwards VI High School

- OCR Level 2 Extended Certificate in IT User Skills
- OCR Level 2 NVQ Certificate in German

(10 GCSEs A-C Including Maths and English) Including:

- Mathematics B
- Further Mathematics C

## **Extra Curricular Activities**

#### **Studying 7 Online Udemy Courses**

To expand my knowledge in these programming languages and frameworks:

- HTML CSS JavaScript
- jQuery Bootstrap Wordpress PHP MySQL APIs Python C#
- Mobile Gaming Apps
- NodeJS AngularJS

#### Skateboarding, Snowboarding and Video Editing

Partaking of and filming of Skateboarding and Snowboarding

- It takes self discipline, self motivation and persistence to learn
- Have already acquired skills and experience filming and editing videos since it has been a hobby of mine since early teenage years

#### **Basketball and Esports**

Playing in a basketball team

Requires intense, fast paced team work